bluecoreinside.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy — BLUECORE INSIDE

The privacy of our visitors to BluecoreInside.com is important to us.

At BluecoreInside.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit BluecoreInside.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

If you have any questions, feel free to reach us at:  
#407,  St907, Toul Sangke. Russey Keo 12105  
Phnom Penh(Cambodia)

 **Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on BluecoreInside.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes and to make messages more relevant to you (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). The technology helps to prevent the same advertisements from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.

Some advertising networks require that we specifically list their opt-out links below:

<https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting:

<http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

 **Phishing**  
We will never ask for your personal information through an email or a social media message.

 _What is phishing?  
_  
Phishing is a scam in which someone pretends to be someone else in order to gain your trust—usually contacting you over email or by message on a social media platform, but also occasionally by a telephone call—with the ultimate goal of stealing your personal or financial information.  
Many companies, like ours, have branded images that are easily recognizable, and scammers have used those images to take phishing to the next level by reaching out to a company’s fans or customers under the guise of that company and using that company’s branded images.

 _How can I detect phishing?  
_  
Identifying a phishing scam is harder than it once was because scammers are getting better at designing emails and messages to look legitimate. But we will never ask for your bank account number, social security number, or any other personal information in an email or message. No matter how official the email or message may look, if the sender asks for personal information, it is likely a phishing scam. Do not reply to or click on links in these emails.

Not every email you receive is a scam, and occasionally you really will need to reach out to a company with regard to your personal information. For instance, we love to do sweepstakes and giveaways, and if we are going to send you prizes, we’ll need to know where to send them. But you don’t have to follow the steps in every email or telephone call—especially the suspicious ones. Instead:

  * Call the company directly. If the company called you, ask to call them right back. When you call back, don’t use the number they gave you. Instead, search for the company online and get the contact information directly off their website.

  * If you have an online account with the company, go to their official website (but not via the link in the email or message!), and log in. Many companies will send important messages to your online account as well as your email.

 _What if I think I’ve been hooked or want to report a scam?  
_  
Contact the institution the phishing email or message was purporting to be. If they have no record of asking for your information, change your account immediately to minimize the damage. If you receive a suspicious email or message purporting to be from us, please forward that message to  
. If the message is sent via a social media platform, please report that message to the respective social media platform for removal.

 _AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by[ **Sec-Source Technologies**](http://sec-source-technologies.com/)._
